So here's the thing. I wore the suit because it is the colors of the Palestinian flag.
Now that I know that Puma is a part of the BDS movement, I will cover up the Puma logo next time.
I keep seeing people say things like the Palestinians need to get rid of Hamas.
So let's break down how absolutely nonsensical that is.
If Hamas is a terrorist group and they're so dangerous, they're so dangerous that Israel, who has the most highest level of weaponry and surveillance, feels unsafe.
So unsafe that they have to genocide anyone who was within spitting distance or just within the idea and perimeters of Hamas.
If they are so dangerous that Israel has to genocide an entire people, what makes you think that those same people would be able to just get rid of Hamas?
You see how dumb that sounds?
You see? You see how dumb that sounds?
That's how dumb y'all sound.
These regular people need to get rid of this group that we consider to be terrorists.
This is what I mean. The Zionist math don't be mathing.
It just adds up to racism.